Jamie Henry

Clermont, Florida, United States



sevenirh@brighthouse.com



linkedin.com/in/jamie-henry-8ba765154

Summary

I am a competitive, and versatile student pursuing a degree in Computer Engineering at the University of Central Florida. I have a passion for computers, technology, video games and I enjoy problem solving and analyzing algorithms. I have experience in Unity and multiple programming languages, such as the skills listed on my profile.

Experience



Server

Olive Garden

Sep 2021 - Apr 2022 (8 months)



Server

Feb 2016 - Sep 2021 (5 years 8 months)

Education



🤵 University of Central Florida

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering Aug 2019 - May 2022



Lake-Sumter State College

Associate's degree, General Studies Aug 2017 - May 2019

Licenses & Certifications



Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp



(A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - freeCodeCamp

Skills

Multitasking • Computer Engineering • Problem Solving • C (Programming Language) • Java • C# • Python (Programming Language) • Data Structures • Time Management • Critical Thinking

Honors & Awards



Mathematics Award - Lake-Sumter State College

Apr 2019

For academic excellence and achievement in mathematics.